[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the maximum amount of memory that could be installed on the 1975 PDP-11/70, one of the most powerful of the popular PDP-11 series, produced by Digital Equipment Corporation?", "correct_answer": "4 MB", "incorrect_answers": ["512 KB", "16 MB", "64 MB"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these celebrities is not Swedish?", "correct_answer": "Lars Ulrich", "incorrect_answers": ["the members of ABBA", "Greta Garbo", "Ingrid Bergman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does an auxologist study?", "correct_answer": "growth", "incorrect_answers": ["money", "flags", "meteorites"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In reference to what was the term pineapple used before it became the name of the tropical fruit?", "correct_answer": "Pine cones", "incorrect_answers": ["Wild apples", "All of these", "Hand grenades"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This character actor starred with Michael Landon in both Little House on the Prairie and Highway to Heaven. The characters he played were Mr. Edwards and Mark Gordon.", "correct_answer": "Victor French", "incorrect_answers": ["Sebastian Cabot", "Will Geer", "Jerry Reed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Barack Obama is a righty.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the fictional early 19th century Swiss family who was shipwrecked on a desert island in the south Pacific?", "correct_answer": "Robinson", "incorrect_answers": ["Mills", "Carouso", "Parkinson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Snakes are this kind of animals.", "correct_answer": "Carnivorous", "incorrect_answers": ["Herbivorous", "Omnivorous", "Vegetarian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Female lions hunt in a group.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country held the record for the highest birth rate in the 2005 world statistics?", "correct_answer": "Niger", "incorrect_answers": ["Uganda", "Mali", "Vatican City"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The highest recorded speed a cheetah has obtained is 80 mph (130 km/h.)", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor starred as Jake in Roman Polanskis 1974 movie Chinatown?", "correct_answer": "Jack Nicholson", "incorrect_answers": ["Marlon Brando", "Dustin Hoffman", "Robert De Niro"]}]